Ildikó Tóth UX Designer

I am a code-savvy, detail-oriented designer in Portland, OR. Pivoting my career to the full spectrum of UX, I am excited to bring my previous experience with engineering together with my more recent UX work to directly design for how users interact with products.

CONTACT

imildi.com

J 703,597,8004

in linkedin.com/in/ildikototh

SKILLS

VISUAL

Adobe(Ps, II,Id)

Axure

Balsamia

Figma

InVision

Paper + Pen

Sketch

DEVELOPMENT

Github

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

jQuery

Python

Ć#

SQL

PRESENTATION

Camtasia

Draw.io

iMovie

Keynote

Powerpoint

PERSONAL

Certified Agile Product Owner

Airbnb Business Owner

Fluent in French and Hungarian

Mazamas Mountaneering Club

Member

EXPERIENCE

InReach Solutions - Designer + Developer

Jan - Jul 2017

UX Research & Coding: Converted customer requests into concrete projects, implemented in SQL.

Layout & Content: Designed print ads, posters, customer e-mail.

Brand Design: Revamped website, logo, business card + made new brand guidelines.

Intel - Business Analyst + Product Owner

Jul 2015 - Jan 2017

Data Visualization: Transformed a multidimensional dataset to visually show a 500k memberhierarchy.

UX Project Management: Designed a location-smart onboarding experience. Developed wireframes, user stories and flows for crossfunctional groups and external design agencies.

Financial Administration: Managed a \$250K service budget

Intel - Automation Software Engineer

Jul 2011 - Jan 2015

Software Engineering: Reduced execution time of manufacturing experiments by 50%.

Machine Learning: Used a proprietary machine learning software to automate material movement models in intel factories.

EDUCATION

Bloc.io 2017 - 2018

UX Design Apprenticeship. Portfolio review & 760 + hrs of experience.

Stanford University & Portland State University 2013 - 2014 Computer Science Courses

University of Paul Sabatier (France) 2010 - 2011 License 3 in General Math. Full French Immersion.

Syracuse University 2006 - 2010

BA Graphic Design + Math. Minor in IT GPA: 3.93/4

